[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "fortunately ... often ... frequently ... usually",
        "answer": "fortunately"
    },
    {
        "question": "because / like / really / argue / roommates / I / my / ever / we / anything / hardly / abou",
        "answer": "I really like my new roommates because we hardly ever argue about anything."
    },
    {
        "question": "my / boyfriend / that / last / forgot / week / birthday / my / nearly / believe / can't / I",
        "answer": "I can't believe that my boyfriend nearly forgot my birthday last week."
    },
    {
        "question": "good / was / school / high / have / I / lucky / extremely / math / to / teacher / in / had / a",
        "answer": "I was extremely lucky to have had a good math teacher in high school."
    },
    {
        "question": "had / we / movie / ever / that / the / was / worst / absolutely / that / seen",
        "answer": "That was absolutely the worst movie that we had ever seen."
    },
    {
        "question": "actually ... under ... behind ... somewhere",
        "answer": "actually"
    },
    {
        "question": "fortunately ... seldom ... rarely ... usually",
        "answer": "fortunately"
    },
    {
        "question": "hourly ... still ... increasingly ... rarely",
        "answer": "increasingly"
    },
    {
        "question": "happily ... calmly ... hourly ... honestly",
        "answer": "hourly"
    },
    {
        "question": "enough ... fully ... yesterday ... very",
        "answer": "yesterday"
    },
    {
        "question": "certainly ... apparently ... occasionally ... honestly",
        "answer": "occasionally"
    },
    {
        "question": "our / it / class / Monday / make / meeting / to / I / unfortunately / cannot / next",
        "answer": "Unfortunately, I cannot make it to our class meeting next Monday."
    }
]